Column description

- name: 			Name of the track
- duration_ms: 			The track length in milliseconds
- explicit: 			Whether or not the track has explicit lyrics (true = yes it does; false = no it does not OR unknown)
- popularity: 			The popularity of a track is a value between 0 and 100, with 100 being the most popular. 
- artists: 			The artists' names who performed the track. If there is more than one artist, they are separated by a ;
- album_name: 	 		The album name in which the track appears
- danceability: 		Danceability describes how suitable a track is for dancing. A value of 0.0 is least danceable and 1.0 is most danceable    
- energy: 			Energy is a measure from 0.0 to 1.0 and represents a perceptual measure of intensity and activity. 
- key:				The key the track is in. Integers map to pitches using standard Pitch Class notation. 
- loudness: 			The overall loudness of a track in decibels (dB)
- mode:				Mode indicates the modality (major or minor) of a track. Major is represented by 1 and minor is 0
- speechiness: 			Speechiness detects the presence of spoken words in a track. 
- acousticness:			A confidence measure from 0.0 to 1.0 of whether the track is acoustic. 1.0 represents high confidence the track is acoustic
- instrumentalness:		Predicts whether a track contains no vocals. The closer the instrumentalness value is to 1.0		
- liveness:			Detects the presence of an audience in the recording. 
- valence:			A measure from 0.0 to 1.0 describing the musical positiveness conveyed by a track. 
- tempo:			The overall estimated tempo of a track in beats per minute (BPM). 
- features_duration_ms: 	The duration of the track in milliseconds
- time_signature:		An estimated time signature. 
- n_beats:			The total number of time intervals of beats throughout the track. 
- n_bars:			The total number of time intervals of the bars throughout the track. 
- popularity_confidence: 	The confidence, from 0.0 to 1.0, of the popularity of the song.
- genre:			The genre in which the track belongs

